Finding Aid for the Fletcher Bascom Dresslar Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Outgoing Correspondence Index
  - Crampton, C. Ward, March 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Goin, J.M., March 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Hyde, Blanche E., March 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - DeLozier, A.O., March 11, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., March 11, 1914 (Box 2)
  - McCulloch, J.E., March 11, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Myers, Winter W., March 11, 1914 (Box 2)
  - NY State Cmsn. on Ventilation, March 11, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Wolcott, John D., March 11, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Binkhart, John L., March 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Grumbine, S.J., March 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ennis, Robert Berry, March 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Fulton, John S., March 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Galloway, E.H., March 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., March 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - McCormack, A.T., March 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Porter, Joseph Y., March 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Sumner, Guilford H., March 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Bracken, H.M., March 13, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., March 13, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Skidmore, V.M., March 13, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Woodward, William C., March 13, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Cogswell, W.F., March 15, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Dalton, Charles F., March 15, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Dixon, Samuel G., March 15, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Dowling, Oscar, March 15, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Hutschcroft, L.W., March 15, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., March 15, 1914 (Box 2)
  - McGurren, C.J., March 15, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Mclaughlin, A.J., March 15, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Williams, Ennion G., March 15, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Arvold, A.G., March 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Bracken, H.M., March 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Drake, C. St. Clair, March 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - State Board of Health, Alabam, March 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ittner, William B., March 17, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ennis, Robert Mary, March 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Falk, Ralph, March 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Gilbert and Betelle, Architects, March 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Green, Frederick R., March 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Hurty, J.N., March 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., March 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Morgenthaler, F.S., March 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Wheeler, Forrest, March 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Beatty, T.B., March 19, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Buerk, A.J., March 19, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Harrison, Katie Belle, March 19, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., March 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Biggs, Hermann M., March 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Moore, E.H., March 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - White, Calvin S., March 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Hunter, Pauli S., March 22, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ellis, Mabel Brown, March 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Myers Winter W., March 25, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Booker, Warren H., March 26, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Brown, J.B., March 26, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., March 26, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Haskins, C.A., March 26, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., March 26, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Maphis, Charles G., March 26, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Naramore, F.A, March 26, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Cramton, C. Ward, March 29, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ellis, Mabel Brown, March 29, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Narmamore, F.A., March 29, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Price, Jacob C., March 29, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Story, T.E., March 29, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ellis, Mabel Brown, March 30, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Brooks, Frankie, March 30, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Church, A.K., March 31, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Gulick, Julia, March 31, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Hatfield, Frank, March 31, 1914 (Box 2)
  - O'Donnell, T.C., March 31, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Martindale, Henrietta, March 31, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Steadwell, B.S., March 31, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Wheeler, Forrest, March 31, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Austral Window Co., April 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., April 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., April 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Snow, W.F., April 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, Jr., April 2, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hatfield, Frank H., April 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hatfield, Frank H., April 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Green, Frederick R., AprilS, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Green, Frederick R., April S, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, B.D., AprilS, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, B.D., AprilS, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Storey, T.E., AprilS, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Franklin, W.S., April 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Pettus, T.V., April 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Tyson, W.E., April 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Arvold, A.G., April 10, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Grumbine, J.C., April 10, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ellis, Mabie Brown, April 10, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hatfield, Frank, April 10, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Philips, C.V., April 10, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, Jr., April 10, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wiles, E.P., April 10, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Green, Frederick R., April 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Green, Frederick R., April 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hatfield, Frank H., April 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Jackson, Isabel, April 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Moulthrop, S.P., April 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Small, Willard S., April 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wilkerson, R.E., April 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Payne, Dr., April 14, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., April 17, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., April 19, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Marsh, J.F., April 20, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hatfield, Frank H., April 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hines, L.N., April 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Miller, James Alex, April 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Rye, Tom C., April 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Small, W.S., April 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., April 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., April 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Marsh, J.F., April 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Blue, Rupert, April 28, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Bruce, William C., April 28, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., April 28, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Pearse, Carroll G., April 28, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, Jr., April 28, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, Jr., April 28, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Self, J.C., April 28, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Shepherd, John W., April 28, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Bancroft, Jessie H., April 29, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Barnes, C.H., April 29, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., May 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Cubberly, Elwood P., May 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., May 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., May 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Donovan, John J., May 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Roach, R.P., May 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Adcock, Sam Y., May 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ayres, Leonard P., May 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Church, H.V., May 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Delozier, A.O., May 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Keene, C.H., May 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., May 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - McCulloch, J.E., May 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Small, W.S., May 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wolcott, J.D., May 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Lund, Haviland H., May 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - NY State Cmsn. on Ventilation, May 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Jenks, C.L., May 6, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., MayS, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., May 6, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Mathews, G.S., May 6, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Roach, R.P., May 6, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wolcott, John D., May 6, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Barnes, C.H., May 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Langslow, H.R., May 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Small, W.S., MayS, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Bancroft, Jesse H., May 11, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Brooks, Frankie, May 12, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., May 15, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Reed, C.E., May 15, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Roach, R.P., May 15, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., May 17, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., May 17, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, Jr., May 17, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Andress, J. Mace, May 18, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., May 18, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Lund, Haviland H., May 18, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wolcott, John D., May 18, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wood, Thomas D., May 18, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Barthram, Frank M., May 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - McTate, Jannie F., May 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hartwell, Harry T., May 22, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., May 24, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wolcott, J.D., May 24, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Adcock, Sam Y., May 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wiggers, J.A., May 27, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hall-Quest, Alfred L., May 28, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, Jr., May 28, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Bancroft, Jesse H., June 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Bartram, Frank M., June 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., June 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Daman, E.O., Jr., June 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Fowler Langslow Co., June 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Healy, Thomas D., June 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - McCulloch, J.E., June 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - McTate, Jannie F., June 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - G. E. Stechert and Co., June 2, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wolcott, John D., June 2, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Andress, J. Mace, June 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Barnes, C.H., June 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Donovan, John J., June 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Mathews, Gertrude, June 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., June 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Healy, Mary L., June 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ittner, William B., June 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., June 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., June 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, Jr., June 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wiggers, J.A., June 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wood, Thomas D., June 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., June 7, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Mayers, David Campbell, June?, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Sturgis and Walton Co., June 7, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Healy, Thomas D., June 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., June 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Foster, James H., June 11, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Morelock, G.L., June 11, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Andress, J. Mace, June 14, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Foster, James H., June 11, 1195 (Box 2)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., June 14, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Payne, Bruce R., June 14, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Stephen, James, June 14, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hartwell, Harry T., June 15, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Cherry, H.H., June 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Diii,J.W., June 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Donovan, Jonathan J., June 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., June 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Langslow, H.R., June 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Roach, R.P., June 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Feminear, Mary, June 23, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., June 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hartwell, Harry T., June 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Martin, Leon A., June 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hartwell, Harry T., June 29, 1915 (Box 2)
  - LeGarde, Ellen, June 29, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Leathers, W.S., June 30, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Lund, Haviland H., June 30, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Luther, Agnes Vinton, June 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Macmillan Co., June 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Schapiro, Louis, June 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Funderburk, Martha, July 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - University of Georgia, July 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Pratt, Thomas P., July 7, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Martin, Leon A., July 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Van Duzor, Charlotte E., July 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., July 16, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Cook, Grant, July 16, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Finley, John L., July 16, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., July 16, 1915 (Box 2)
  - LeGarde, Ellen, July 16, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Smith, Austin W., July 16, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Corwin, R.W., July 19, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Manning, Frank A., July 19, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Nunn, Roscoe, July 19, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Small, W.S., July 19, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Smith, Austin W., July 19, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, July 23, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Smith, Austin W., July 23, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Turlington, Ira T., July 23, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Smith, Austin W., July 27, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Colebanks, C.H., July 31, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Smith, Austin W., July 31, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Stuaart, M.H., July 31, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ballard, S. Thruston, Oct. 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Barker, Blanche Wiggin, Oct. 13, 1195 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Oct. 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Harmon, J.C., Oct. 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Oct. 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wright, Robert H., Oct. 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Battson, J.M., Oct. 14, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Bennett, L.E., Oct. 14, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Broaddus, Mrs. H., Oct. 14, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Monroe, Robert C., Oct. 14, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Morris, Frank A., Oct. 14, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Purdam, B.K., Oct. 14, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Rapeer, Louis W., Oct. 14, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Shaw, John C., Oct. 14, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Sugg, H.B., Oct. 14, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wray, Joe S., Oct. 14, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Oct. 19, 1915 (Box 2)
  - J.H. Felt and Co., Oct. 19, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Oct. 19, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Oct. 191, 195 (Box 2)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Oct. 19, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Andress, J. Mace, Oct. 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - McLeskey, W.B., Nov. 2, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Gayle, E.F., Nov. 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Axel, Nov. 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ballard, S. Thurston, Nov. 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Bishop, Fred G., Dec. 2, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Howell, Harry, Dec. 2, 1915 (Box 2)
  - McCulloch, J.E., Dec. 2, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Shawkey, M.P., Dec. 2, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Dec. 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Linn, W.B., Dec. 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Walker, Lula, Dec. 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wright, Robert H., Dec. 3, 1195 (Box 2)
  - Ittner, W.B., Dec. 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Purdum, B.K., Dec. 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Judson, Dec. 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Rudd, Channing, Dec. 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Donald, James T., Dec. 16, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Dec. 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Lund, Haviland H., Dec. 22, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Smith, A.J., Dec. 22, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Shackelford, Mr., Dec. 23, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Dec. 27, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., 1915, undated (Box 2)
  - King, Jeannette M., 1915, undated (Box 2)
  - Manley, Ida M., 1915, undated (Box 2)
  - Pace, Johnson, H., 1915, undated (Box 2)
  - Peelle, Stanton J., Jan. 6, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Barnes, F.B., Jan. 10, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Hatcher, J.F., Jan. 13, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Diffenbaugh, Mr., Jan. 14, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Kinsley, NFN, Jan. 17, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Hatcher, J.F., Jan. 24, 1916 (Box 2)
  - King, Miss, Jan. 24, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Minnich, O.C., Jan. 24, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Hackett, Frank S., Jan. 25, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Barnes, John G., Jan. 27, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Hankins, W.O., Jan. 27, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Peele, Stanton J., Jan. 27, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Sense, Mr., Jan. 27, 1916 (Box 2)
  - McDougle, E.C., Jan. 29, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Murphy, Mr., Feb. 10, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Moore, J. Alex, March 4, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Galbreath, President, March 6, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Moore, J. Alex, March 6, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Putnam, Helen G., March 7, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Hall, F.M., March 8, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Heald, Arthur A., March 8, 1916 (Box 2)
  - March, William H., March 8, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Muller, Herman, March 8, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Putnam, Helen G., March 8, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Rich, Ednah A., March 8, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Sheldon, Dr., March 8, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Billie, Edward Fournier, March 9, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Perrine, C.H., March 9, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Tenney, Ross L., March 9, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Suhrie, Ambrose L., March 10, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Lund, Haviland H., March 14, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Moore, J. Alex, March 15, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Moore, J. Alex, March 15, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Diegaard and Rinding, March 16, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Guss, Margaret, March 16, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Haynes, Barney S., March 16, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Bancroft, Jessie H., March 24, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Howell, Harry, March 24, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Moore, J. Alex, March 24, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Neimchesky, L.J., March 24, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Norton, H.B., March 24, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Robinson, W.G., March 24, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Samuelson, Agnes, March 27, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wardlaw, J.C., March 28, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Douglas, A.E., March 30, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Moore, Mr., March 30, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Stewart, March 30, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Burkes, Jennie, April 8, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Keith, C.A., April 8, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Bain, Samuel M., April 11, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Montandon, Charles A., April 11, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Moore, J. Alex, April 11, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, April 11, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wardlaw, J.C., April 12, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Barnes, John G., April 18, 1916 (Box 2)
  - McMillan, Henry, April 18, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wardlaw, J.C., April 18, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Webb, Susana, April 18, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Hatfield, Frank H., April 24, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wardlaw, J.C., April 24, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wood, Thomas D., April 24, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Graves, T.D., April 25, 1916 (Box 2)
  - McNutty, T.E., April 25, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wardlaw, J.C., April 25, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Washburn, J.L., April 25, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Welton, William Lesley, April 25, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Rapp, E.M., April 27, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Hatfield, Frank H., April 29, 1916 (Box 2)
  - McLure, John R., April 29, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Rudd, Channing, April 29, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wardlaw, J.C., April 29, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wardlaw, J.C., May 3, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., May 11, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Henry, D.R., May 11, 1916 (Box 2)
  - McLain, Mr., May 11, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Phillips, C.A., May 11, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Putnam, Herbert L., May 11, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Ranck, F.E., May 11, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wardlaw, J.C., May 11, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Cassell, R.B., May 13, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Foght, Harold W., May 18, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Green, L.E., May 22, 1916 (Box 2)
  - McCulley, Ruth A., May 22, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wardlaw, J.C., May 22, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wardlaw, Mr., May 26, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Dadisman, S.H., May 30, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Gauntt, James G., May 30, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Harrison, NFN, May 30, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Lewis, E.M., May 31, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wardlaw, J.C., May 31, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wardlaw, J.C., June 6, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Stewart, June 7, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Hollis, S.P., June 13, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Keithly, E.W., June 13, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wardlaw, J.C., June 13, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Milligan, R.M., July 1, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Johnston, Helen, July 5, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., July 18, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Monee, U.L., July 31, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Hamilton, Carline M., Aug. 1, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Nichols, Mr., Aug. 1, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Baker, N.R., Aug. 10, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Moore, J. Alex, Aug 10, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Stewart, Alexander T., Aug. 10, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Traweek, P.B., Aug. 10, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Talbott, W.R., Aug. 19, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Howey, E.W., Aug. 21, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Price, Warren, Aug. 26, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Gilbert, Mr., Aug. 26, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Ellis, A. Caswell, Aug. 28, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Copeland, Ada B., Aug. 31, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Barefield, M.D., Sept. 24, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Miller, Charles E., Sept. 24, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Ratliff, F.C., Sept. 29, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Dunaway, Mr., Oct. 9, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Dunn, W.W., Oct. 9, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Moore, I.P., Oct. 9, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Talbott, W.R., Oct. 14, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Payne, Dr., Oct. 18, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, NFN, Oct. 22, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wood, Frank H., Oct. 22, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Payne, Dr., Oct. 31, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Dunnaway, O.L., Nov. 1, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Henderson, M.T., Nov. 4, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Muerman, Dr., Nov. 4, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Varney, Penn, Nov. 4, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wood, Dr., Nov. 4, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Groos, Alfred W., Nov. 6, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Rule, Lillian, Nov. 6, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Sullivan, Louis H., Nov. 6, 1916 (Box 2)
  - McKenzie, F.A., Nov. 7, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Watkins, W.H., Nov. 9, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wilkinson, W.A., Nov. 9, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Dunaway, O.L., Nov. 13, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Spencer, Raymond B., Dec. 11, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Bancroft, Jessie H., Dec. 18, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Budd, Nora, Dec. 18, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Edwards, Frank L., Dec. 18, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Kind, Grace, Dec. 18, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Latham, R.H., Dec. 18, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Lund, Haviland H., Dec. 18, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Moore, J.A., Dec. 18, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Swarts, Gardner T., Jr., Dec. 18, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Ray, S.W., Dec. 20, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Payne, Bruce R., Dec. 29, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Ramsey, H.D., 1916, undated (Box 2)
  - Dreisbach, J.F., Jan. 1, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Dunaway, O.L., Jan. 8, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Dunaway, O.L., Jan. 9, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Dunaway, O.L., Jan. 12, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Jan. 13, 1917 (Box 2)
  - King, Grace, Jan. 20, 1917 (Box 2)
  - McDonald, W.R., Jan. 24, 1917 (Box 2)
  - West,A.F., Jan. 24, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Smyth, Jefferson L., Jan. 25, 1917 (Box 2)
  - McDonald, W.R., Jan. 29, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Alleman, L.J., Feb. 2, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Ittner, W.B., Feb. 2, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Wilson, C.E., Feb. 3, 1917 (Box 2)
  - McDonald, Mr., Feb. 10, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Smith, Edith, Feb. 10, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Wardlaw, J.C., Feb. 12, 1917 (Box 2)
  - McClure, Mr., Feb. 20, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Sleight, George N., Feb. 20, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Roy, V.L., Feb. 23, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Bennett, H.E., Feb. 24, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Lee, Joseph, Feb. 24, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Paul, August E., Feb. 24, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Putnam, Helen C., Feb. 24, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Schoenhals, M.K., March 12, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Wolcott, John D., March 12, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., March 16, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Lindberg, Lydia, March 17, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., March 26, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Ellis, Mabel Brown, March 26, 1916 (Box 2)
  - Hall, R.C., March 26, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Nichol, Julia H., April 19, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Sisson, E.O., May 16, 1917 (Box 2)
  - McClure, John R., May 25, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Webster, Joseph, May 31, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., July 15, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Goldsberry, Mrs., July 19, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Aug. 17, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Porter, Mr., Aug. 28, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Sept. 25, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Feagin, W.F., Sept. 28, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Boykin, J.C., Oct. 27, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Blount, Villma, Nov. 5, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Baish, H.H., Nov. 19, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Hargraves, J.J., Nov. 19, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Kistler, A.H., Nov. 30, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Wood, Thomas D., March 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Barnwell, C.H., March 31, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Devendorf, B.A., March 31, 1913 (Box 1)
  - N.O. Nelson Manufacturing Co., March 31, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Speed, James, March 31, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Thompson, Nath, March 31, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wolff and Company, March 31, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, Wales C., April 2, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., April 2, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McCloskey, Alice G., April 2, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., April 2, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Robinson, J.E., April 2, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Speed, James, April 2, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Greeley, Allan, April 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., April 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., April 4, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Small, Willard S., April 4, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Duncan, George W., April 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., April 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas Denison, April 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Perrett, T.E., April 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., April 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Cheney, Charles H., April 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Fegley, H. Winslow, April 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Hillyer, Thomas A., April 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kerns, Marshall, April 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ludlow and Peabody, April 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, W.C., April 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Caldwell, James E., April 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., April 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Doelle, Jonathan A., April 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Roderick, J.F., April 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Yasinski, A.F., April 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Boykin, J.C., April 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Cheney, Charles H., April 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., April 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., April 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McCloskey, Alice G., April 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Pullman Ventilator Mfg. Co., April 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Monahan, A.C., April 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Payne, Bruce R., April 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., April 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., April 16, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., April 16, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Barber, Charles I., April 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Keboch, F.D., April 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., April 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., April 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, W.C., April 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Newman, Montrose K., April 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Boykin, J.C., April 19, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Fegley, H. Winslow, April 19, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Corwin, R.W., April 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McCloskey, Alice G., April 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Thomas, C.W., April 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas Denison, April 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Bruce, William George, April 23, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Cheney, Charles H., April 23, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., April 23, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McCloskey, Alice G., April 23, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., April 23, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, W.C., April 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Boykin, J.C., April 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Henry E., April 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Doelle, Jonathan A., April 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Mark, E.H., April 24, 1913 (Box 1)